President
대통령
"Catch outside the ring"
"링 밖에서 잡아라"
Damn. unbelievable
젠장. 믿을 수 없는
Mr. Bai.
바이 씨.
Give me the address of the woman who runs the café.
카페를 운영하는 아주머니 주소를 알려주세요.
These two idiots are ready to fight.
이 두 바보는 싸울 준비가 되어있습니다.
You scoundrels.
악당들아.
You bastards!
이 개자식들!
the curse
저주
Come closer, you idiot!
가까이 와, 바보야!
Screw you, you bastards! ‬
엿먹어라, 이 개자식들아! ‬
Damn
젠장
You bastard
이 새끼야
- They attacked him at the same time! - You scoundrel.
- 동시에 공격했어요! - 이 악당놈아.
the curse
저주
You fools!
멍청이 들아!
Come closer!
더 가까이 오세요!
Scoundrel!
악당!
damn you
젠장
Beat him up!
그를 때려눕혀라!
You trifle!
당신은 사소한 일입니다!
You scoundrel!
이 악당!
the curse
저주
- You bastard! - You scoundrel!
- 이 개자식아! - 이 악당!
Damn
젠장
You idiot...
당신은 바보...
Come closer!
더 가까이 오세요!
Screw it!
나사로 고정!
stand up! Move
일어나! 이동하다
- Let's leave, Gun-woo. - Okay.
- 가자 건우야 - 알았어
- Let's go!
- 가자! - 알았어.
Thanks for coming, Hyun Joo.
와줘서 고마워요, 현주 씨.
I apologize for coming late.
늦게 와서 사과드립니다.
You saved us from a severe beating.
당신은 심한 구타로부터 우리를 구해 주셨습니다.
How painful. the curse
얼마나 고통스럽습니까. 저주
Is that you, Gun Woo?
건우씨인가요?
"Gunwoo"?
"건우"?
Shut up.
입 다물어.
- Move quickly. - Yes, sir.
- 빨리 움직여요 - 네, 선생님
Hey you
안녕 당신
Who is this
누구세요
How annoying.
얼마나 짜증나는지.
the curse
저주
Wait.
기다리다.
Damn
젠장
Who are you
누구세요
Shut your mouth, you bastard.
입 다물어, 이 새끼야.
stand up
일어서다
Oh God, stop!
맙소사, 그만해요!
What a view.
경치 죽이네.
Hey you
안녕 당신
who are you
누구세요
- Sorry, sir. - Stop.
- 죄송해요 - 그만해요
I asked you a question.
내가 당신에게 질문을했습니다.
sleep well
잘 자다
What? What is this
무엇? 이게 뭔가요
When did you get this beating?
언제 이런 구타를 받았나요?
Dear mom
사랑하는 엄마
Yes, mom.
네 엄마.
“Gun-woo.”
“건우.”
My mom? What happened? Why are you crying?
우리 엄마? 무슨 일이에요? 왜 울고 있어요?
Someone wants to talk to you.
누군가 당신과 이야기하고 싶어합니다.
where are you
어디세요
“Gun-woo.”
“건우.”
What happened to your forehead, mom?
엄마 이마는 어떻게 됐어요?
I'm fine
잘 지내요
My head hit the ground.
내 머리가 땅에 닿았습니다.
your face
너의 얼굴
What happened to your face, Woo Jin?
우진아 얼굴은 어떻게 됐어?
It's just a scratch.
그냥 긁힌 자국이에요.
Mr. Choi felt very anxious while waiting for you.
최 선생님은 당신을 기다리는 동안 매우 불안해하셨습니다 .
Let's go down.
내려 가자.
Well
글쎄요 _
I'll come back
나는 돌아올 것이다
Sit down, everyone!
모두 앉으세요!
I'm sure you're very tired so I'll keep it short.
많이 피곤하실 것 같아서 짧게 말씀드리겠습니다.
When I received your call,
당신의 전화를 받았을 때,
I was shocked as if the world had ended.
나는 세상이 끝난 것처럼 충격을 받았다.
you are my family
당신은 내 가족입니다
I was so afraid of losing you.
나는 당신을 잃을 까봐 너무 두려웠습니다.
I will no longer tolerate you getting hurt.
나는 더 이상 당신이 상처받는 것을 용납하지 않을 것입니다.
Let the adults handle the rest.
나머지는 어른들이 처리하도록 하세요.
-I want to help too. -Gun-woo.
-나도 돕고 싶어요.- 건우.
This is not a game that ends with a win or a loss.
이것은 승패로 끝나는 게임이 아니다.
This is a war that will not end until someone dies.
누군가가 죽을 때까지 끝나지 않는 전쟁이다.
Go upstairs.
위층으로 올라가.
- I'm sorry. - Promise me not to get yourself involved again.
- 미안해요 - 다시는 연루되지 않기로 약속해요
Good
좋은
They know where Gun Woo lives , so it's dangerous to go there.
건우가 사는 곳을 알고 있어서 거기 가는 건 위험해요.
Take Gun Woo's mother to the orphanage tomorrow.
내일 건우 엄마를 고아원에 데려가세요.
It would be safer for her to stay there.
그녀는 그곳에 머무르는 것이 더 안전할 것입니다.
Good
좋은
good night
안녕히 주무세요
What do we do now, Yang Jung?
이제 우리 어떡해요, 양정 씨?
I'll put an end to it.
나는 그것을 끝내겠습니다.
We should have taken care of this a long time ago.
우리는 이 문제를 오래 전에 처리했어야 했습니다 .
Can you bring Myung-gil?
명길씨 데려가실 수 있나요?
I'll be forming a team with Do Young starting tomorrow.
내일부터 도영이랑 팀을 구성할 거예요.
- I'll target them one by one. - Let's eat with Do Young.
- 하나씩 공략해볼게요 - 도영이랑 같이 먹자
Mr. Oh.
오 씨.
Investigate Myeong-gil's men, please.
명길의 부하들을 조사해주세요.
Yes sir.
알겠습니다.
I see you there since early morning , Mr. Director.
이른 아침부터 뵙습니다 , 국장님.
I had to come for you, Mr. Kim.
김 선생님을 데리러 와야 했어요.
I operated on them myself.
나는 그것들을 직접 수술했습니다.
Good. I thank you
좋은. 감사합니다
One of them had the Achilles tendons in both feet cut with a knife.
그 중 한 명은 칼로 양쪽 발의 아킬레스건을 절단한 상태였습니다 .
The tendons in my other shoulder were torn.
다른 쪽 어깨의 힘줄이 찢어졌습니다.
His hair is short
그의 머리는 짧다
His eyes are narrow.
그의 눈은 좁다.
He was fast moving.
그는 빠르게 움직이고 있었습니다.
His knife skills are excellent.
그의 칼솜씨는 탁월하다.
Yes, actually...
네, 실제로는...
It looked more like a sashimi knife.
생선회 칼처럼 보였습니다.
Damn
젠장
Ask Beom to go to the office at one o'clock.
범이에게 1시에 사무실로 가라고 하세요 .
- Let's meet. - Yes, sir.
- 만나요 - 네, 선생님
What is happening has become interesting.
무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 흥미로워졌습니다.
- Finish this. - Okay.
- 이걸 끝내세요 - 알았어
my lord
군주
Yes
예
I will accompany you.
나는 당신과 동행할 것입니다.
Stay here.
여기있어.
I want to help sir.
선생님을 돕고 싶습니다.
“Min Dong.”
“민동.”
I'll take care of it myself.
내가 직접 처리하겠습니다.
Live your life
너의 삶을 살아
I want to join you sir!
함께하고 싶습니다 선생님!
Listen
듣다
If the restaurant is destroyed by my return,
내가 돌아오는 바람에 식당이 망가졌다면,
So what will you do?
그래서 너는 뭘 할 껀데?
Protect the store. You can help me with this.
매장을 보호하세요. 당신이 나를 도와줄 수 있습니다.
But
하지만
Guard the store.
가게를 지키세요.
“Yang Jung Huang!”
“양정황!”
It's been a while.
오랜만이야.
Why haven't you been contacting me?
왜 나한테 연락 안 했어?
I was busy making a living.
나는 생계를 유지하느라 바빴습니다.
Why does your handsome face show signs of aging?
잘생긴 얼굴에 노화의 흔적이 보이는 이유는 무엇인가요?
Earning a halal livelihood is difficult.
할랄 생계를 유지하는 것은 어렵습니다.
is not it
안 그래
It's very difficult.
너무 어려워요.
- It's been a long time. - Yes.
- 오랜만이에요 - 네
I called Soo Cheol and Min Soo to ask them to investigate.
수철과 민수에게 전화를 걸어 조사를 요청했다.
It's very complicated.
매우 복잡합니다.
They are not ordinary moneylenders, there is something fishy about them.
그들은 평범한 대금업자가 아니며 뭔가 수상한 점이 있습니다.
Thanks
감사해요
A friend of mine heard in "Youido"
내 친구가 "유이도"에서 들었어
The Il Group purchased an unfinished hotel building in Gangnam.
일그룹이 강남의 미완성 호텔 건물을 매입했다.
They got their money from a company called Smile Capital.
그들은 Smile Capital이라는 회사로부터 돈을 받았습니다.
It's Myung Gil Kim's company.
김명길 회사입니다.
Okay
좋아요
But why would a chaebol borrow money from Myung Gil Kim? I don't understand it.
그런데 왜 재벌이 김명길에게 돈을 빌렸겠는가? 나는 그것을 이해하지 못한다.
Most likely, Myung-Gil Kim tricked them.
아마도 김명길이 그들을 속였을 것이다.
- Let's investigate. - Okay.
- 조사해보자 - 알았어
We will finally avenge our men.
우리는 마침내 우리 부하들의 복수를 할 것입니다.
Let's end this issue.
이 문제를 끝내겠습니다.
Mr. Choi gave us his approval.
최 선생님께서 우리를 승인해 주셨어요.
Good
좋은
In the past, Chairman Choi had five appellants working for him.
과거 최 회장 에게는 5명의 항소인이 있었다.
At that time, President Choi had loaned money to companies,
당시 최 회장은 기업에 돈을 빌려줬고,
He now has 10 billion won or more in uncollected money.
현재 그에게는 회수되지 않은 돈이 100억 원이 넘는다 .
But places like real estate companies had gangs
하지만 부동산 회사 같은 곳에는 갱단이 있었어요
To guard her.
그녀를 보호하기 위해.
And at times like this, these guys come out.
그리고 이럴때 이런놈들이 나옵니다.
They go out to eliminate an entire gang in a day.
그들은 하루 안에 갱 전체를 제거하러 나갑니다.
At that time, even the major gangs were trembling in fear of stabbing Chairman Choi.
당시에는 주요 갱단들조차 최 회장을 찌를까 두려워 떨고 있었다.
After I removed President Choi,
최 회장을 해임한 뒤,
The first thing I did with “Byom”
제가 'Byom'으로 가장 먼저 한 일은
He is getting rid of his attackers.
그는 공격자를 제거하고 있습니다.
Do you know why?
이유를 아시나요?
No sir.
아닙니다.
Because I was trembling in fear of them too.
나 역시 그들이 두려워 떨고 있었기 때문이다.
Were you alone?
혼자였나요?
We sent two gangs, one from Sindang-dong and the other from Yeongdeungpo, and they were united.
우리는 신당동에서 한 명, 영등포에서 한 명씩 두 패를 파견하여 하나로 뭉쳤습니다.
It only came about because they weren't together at the time.
그 당시에 그들이 함께 있지 않았기 때문에 일어난 것입니다 .
Otherwise, it would be impossible to achieve this.
그렇지 않으면 이를 달성하는 것이 불가능합니다.
Wow, how wonderful, sir.
와, 정말 훌륭해요 선생님.
But in the end,
그러나 결국,
I couldn't get rid of the two most important ones.
가장 중요한 두 가지를 버릴 수가 없었습니다.
Do Young Lee and Yang Jung Hwang.
이도영, 황양정.
They are President Choi's right hand.
최 회장의 오른팔이다.
I met Do Young Lee once when I was Chairman Choi's servant.
나는 최 회장의 하인이었을 때 이도영을 한 번 만났다 .
he is handsome
그는 잘 생긴입니다
One time, there was a gang leader who was stuck in a traffic jam.
한번은 교통체증에 갇힌 갱단의 두목이 있었습니다.
He smoked a cigarette with the car window open.
그는 차 창문을 열어둔 채 담배를 피웠다.
When he heard the sound of a motorcycle approaching, he turned his head.
오토바이가 다가오는 소리가 들리자 그는 고개를 돌렸다.
Then Do Young Lee slit his face like this with a sashimi knife and walked away.
그러자 이도영은 회칼로 얼굴을 이렇게 자르고 걸어 나갔다.
His mouth grew so large and began to tremble like this.
입이 너무 커지고 이렇게 떨리기 시작했다.
Damn, crazy.
젠장, 미쳤어.
-And who is Yang Jung Hwang? -It is actually said...
-그리고 양정황은 누구인가? -실제로도 말하는데...
He incapacitated 20 gangsters
그는 갱스터 20명을 무력화시켰습니다.
By tearing the Achilles tendons.
아킬레스건을 찢어서 말이죠.
He fights with two knives,
두 개의 칼을 들고 싸우는데,
It is rumored that he stabs 100 times a minute.
1분에 100번씩 찌른다고 합니다.
It's amazing and wondrous.
놀랍고 경이롭습니다.
correct. Did you say those three guys showed up?
옳은. 그 세 사람이 나타났다고 했죠?
Yes sir. A young woman appeared after some time passed.
알겠습니다. 시간이 흐른 뒤 젊은 여성이 나타났다.
I think it has something to do with the bookstore I told you about before.
아까 말했던 서점과 관련이 있는 것 같아요 .
It makes sense that he would own a bookstore.
그가 서점을 소유하게 된 것은 당연한 일이다.
Surely that damned senile old man crawled out of the darkness to save his children.
확실히 그 빌어먹을 노쇠한 노인은 자기 아이들을 구하기 위해 어둠 속에서 기어나왔습니다.
Do you know how much President Choi owns?
최 회장이 얼마나 소유하고 있는지 아시나요?
Nearly 50 billion won in cash I think.
현금으로 500억 원 정도 되는 것 같아요.
This will save us money for the club.
이렇게 하면 클럽 비용을 절약할 수 있습니다 .
Surely there is a force in heaven looking after us, don't you think?
확실히 하늘에는 우리를 지켜주는 힘이 있다고 생각하지 않나요?
Jang Do and Beom monitored the place and brought me everything there.
장도와 범이가 그 장소를 감시하고 모든 것을 그곳으로 가져왔습니다.
"Loving Orphanage"
"사랑의 고아원"
Will not you come
당신은 오지 않을 것인가?
I don't want to enter. Hurry up!
나는 들어가고 싶지 않다. 서둘러요!
Good. We'll be right back.
좋은. 곧 돌아오겠습니다.
- From here, children. - Look at this.
- 여기부터 얘들아 - 이것 좀 봐
Please come from here.
여기에서 오세요.
It is a children's room so it is a bit small.
아이들방이라 좀 좁네요.
But it is suitable for residence, so take your time to inspect it.
하지만 주거용으로는 적합하므로 시간을 갖고 점검해 보세요.
Thanks
감사해요
What do you think about this place, mom? Look, it's Woo Jin.
엄마 여기 어때요? 보세요, 우진이에요.
Hello ma'am
안녕하세요 부인
A friend of mine from middle school
내 중학교 친구야
He works for one of Myung-gil Kim's men, so he was on the scene that day.
그는 김명길의 부하 중 한 명과 함께 일하기 때문에 그날 현장에 있었습니다.
What I heard was that the situation had reached a terrifying level.
제가 들은 얘기는 상황이 무서운 수준에 이르렀다는 것이었습니다.
They were waiting for him at the gas station.
그들은 주유소에서 그를 기다리고 있었습니다.
As soon as the Ile heir entered,
Ile 상속인이 들어오 자마자
They imprisoned him, beat him, and threatened him.
그들은 그를 투옥하고 구타하고 위협했습니다.
They must be the only ones in Korea who would do this to a chaebol.
재벌에게 이런 짓을 할 사람은 한국에서 그들밖에 없을 것이다 .
and what else
그리고 또 뭐
They have a video of the man...
그 남자 영상이 있는데..
This is Jun Min Kim, Sales Director at Smile Capital.
스마일캐피탈 영업이사 김준민 입니다 .
He has six records of fraud.
그는 사기 전과가 6개나 있다.
Scams related to used cars and credit cards, and he did not leave any type of them without practicing them.
중고차, 신용카드 관련 사기를 쳤고 , 어떤 종류의 사기도 연습하지 않고 방치하지 않았다.
He apparently served his detention in the Seoul Nambu detention center.
그는 서울 남부 구치소에서 구금된 것으로 보인다 .
Jang Do Im was a student at the Police College.
장도임은 경찰대학 학생이었습니다.
Until he was fired due to sexual harassment.
성희롱으로 해고되기 전까지는요.
He has no previous records and is the head of strategic planning at Smile Capital.
그는 이전 경력이 없으며 Smile Capital의 전략 기획 책임자입니다 .
It's unusual.
특이한데요.
The presence of a person familiar with how the police work
경찰의 업무 방식을 잘 아는 사람의 존재
It will help them avoid police investigations.
경찰 조사를 피하는 데 도움이 될 것입니다.
Are these two people important?
이 두 사람이 중요한가요?
Yes
예
What about their address?
주소는 어떻게 되나요?
I came up with this guy's address.
이 사람 주소를 알아냈어요.
He lives in Saesong-dong.
그는 새송동에 산다.
We know his car and its plate number.
우리는 그의 차와 번호판을 알고 있습니다.
We must act quickly.
우리는 빨리 행동해야 합니다.
They will realize what is happening soon.
그들은 곧 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 깨닫게 될 것입니다.
Okay
좋아요
I'll take care of this guy.
이 사람은 내가 처리할게.
- Tomorrow night? - But what limit do we have in dealing with them?
- 내일 밤? - 그런데 우리가 그 사람들을 처리하는 데는 어떤 한계가 있습니까?
what do you mean? We must eliminate them once and for all.
무슨 뜻이에요? 우리는 그들을 완전히 제거해야 합니다.
I'll take care of Myung Gil Kim.
김명길은 제가 책임지겠습니다.
He does not move alone.
그는 혼자 움직이지 않습니다.
What he appears to be different from what he is. Go with Do Young.
실제와 다르게 보이는 것, 도영과 함께 가세요.
I'll just track him down.
그냥 그를 추적하겠습니다.
Wasn't there a burly person with Myung-gil?
명길과 함께 건장한 사람이 있지 않았나요?
Okay
좋아요
The detective agency asked for more time.
탐정사무소에서는 시간을 더 달라고 요청했습니다.
I will investigate further.
더 자세히 조사하겠습니다.
who is he
그 사람은 누구입니까?
He's the man who threw me out the window and he's strong as a bull.
그 사람은 나를 창밖으로 내던진 사람 이고 황소처럼 강한 사람이에요.
Sir, what are you going to do with the money in the bookstore?
선생님, 서점에 있는 돈으로 무엇을 하시겠습니까 ?
We must move it.
우리는 그것을 움직여야 합니다.
He knows the place.
그는 그 장소를 알고 있습니다.
Why don't we ask young people to move money?
젊은이들에게 돈을 옮겨달라고 요청하는 것은 어떨까요?
The problem is that we do not have time and we lack manpower.
문제는 시간도 없고 인력도 부족하다는 점이다.
They are strong.
그들은 강하다.
- They got rid of 30 men. - Did you see what happened?
- 30명을 제거했어요 - 무슨 일이 일어났는지 보셨나요?
I went there but they were lying on the ground.
가봤는데 바닥에 누워 있었어요.
The three of them were surrounded by 30 men and without knives...
그 세 명은 칼도 없이 30명의 남자들에게 둘러싸여 있었는데...
They are not ordinary guys.
그들은 평범한 사람들이 아닙니다.
They won't have a problem if they move the money early in the morning, sir.
아침 일찍 돈을 옮기면 문제가 없을 겁니다 .
Why not give them a chance?
그들에게 기회를 주면 어떨까요?
Hyun Joo is smart too.
현주도 똑똑해요.
Okay, let's put it here.
좋아, 여기에 넣자.
Please.
제발.
It looks delicious.
맛있어 보이네요.
thank you
감사합니다 감사 합니다
- Thank you. - Pardon, hurry up and eat.
- 고마워요 - 죄송해요, 빨리 식사하세요.
You first, Hyun Joo.
먼저 현주야.
Fine, thank you
좋아요, 고마워요
Did you use kimchi to prepare it?
김치를 준비하셨나요?
Yes
예
It tastes completely different from the one I was making.
제가 만든거랑 맛이 완전 다르네요.
The method is easy. I will teach it to you.
방법은 쉽습니다. 나는 그것을 당신에게 가르칠 것입니다.
Good
좋은
I wanted to inquire about something.
뭔가 물어보고 싶었어요.
Is Mr. Choi running the orphanage?
최씨가 고아원을 운영하고 있나요?
Yes
예
My grandfather was poor, according to his words.
그의 말대로 나의 할아버지는 가난했다.
His dream was to help those in need if he had abundant money.
그의 꿈은 돈이 풍부하면 어려운 사람들을 돕는 것이었습니다 .
Good
좋은
Are you his granddaughter then?
그럼 당신은 그 사람의 손녀인가요?
no. I was transferred to the orphanage after my parents died.
아니요. 부모님이 돌아가신 후 고아원으로 옮겨졌습니다.
Good. I'm sorry
좋은. 죄송합니다
Oh God. I shouldn't have brought this up.
오 맙소사. 내가 이 얘기를 꺼내지 말았어야 했는데.
Never mind.
괜찮아요.
I'm sorry
죄송합니다
What food do you like, Hyun Joo?
현주 씨는 어떤 음식을 좋아해요?
In reality
실제로는
I love rolled omelettes.
저는 롤 오믈렛을 좋아해요.
Good. Eat some of these.
좋은. 이것들 중 일부를 먹어보세요.
Wow! Where is the rolled omelette?
우와! 굴린 오믈렛은 어디에 있나요?
You both had to leave some for Hyun Joo.
너희 둘 다 현주한테 좀 남겨야 했어.
This is correct. I wanted her.
이것은 정확합니다. 나는 그녀를 원했다.
Let me prepare more for you.
당신을 위해 더 많이 준비하겠습니다.
It's not your fault
네 잘못이 아니야
No, it won't take long. Wait a minute.
아니요, 오래 걸리지 않습니다. 잠깐 기다려요.
Make it big and thick, mom.
크고 두껍게 만들어 주세요, 엄마.
Good
좋은
Prepare a lot please.
많이 준비해주세요.
Okay, I'll make it big.
알았어, 크게 해볼게.
Hurry up and eat.
서둘러서 먹어라.
“Go to the bookstore the day after tomorrow and transfer all the money.”
“ 내일 모레 서점에 가서 돈을 다 이체하세요.”
"(Jun Min Kim)"
"(김준민)"
take care of yourself
몸 조심하세요
- Have you packed everything? - Yes.
- 짐은 다 쌌어요? - 네.
the curse. it's scary
저주. 무서워
Start making boxes. I'll bring the money.
상자 만들기를 시작하세요. 돈은 내가 가져올게.
How are we going to get her to the car?
그녀를 차로 어떻게 데려가나요?
We will carry it.
우리는 그것을 가지고 갈 것입니다.
No, this will take too long. Vehicle security?
아니요, 시간이 너무 오래 걸립니다. 차량 보안?
Yes. It's in the storage room at the bottom left.
예. 왼쪽 아래 창고에 있어요 .
Woo Jin and I will go get her.
우진이랑 내가 데리러 갈게.
Arrange the money on the floor.
돈을 바닥에 정리하세요.
- Okay. - Come on.
- 알았어 - 어서
How strong you are.
당신은 얼마나 강합니까?
What do you do
너 뭐하니
Don't let him catch you.
그 사람이 당신을 붙잡도록 두지 마세요.
- Who is he? - The man I told you about then.
- 그 사람은 누구죠? - 그때 말했던 그 사람이에요.
the curse
저주
Hit and dodge more quickly.
더 빠르게 공격하고 피하세요.
Good
좋은
You bastard.
이 개자식.
Damn
젠장
just chill. Stop, that's enough.
그냥 진정해. 그만해, 그거면 충분해
its enough
충분 해
just chill
그냥 진정해
it's all over
모든 끝났어
All is well
모두 잘 지내요
- Let's tie him up. - Yes.
- 묶자 - 응
- Let's find something to tie him to. - Okay.
- 그 사람을 묶을 만한 걸 찾아보자 - 알았어.
- Go check that side.
- 가서 저쪽을 확인해 보세요 - 알았어
the curse
저주
"Woo Jin!"
"우진!"
critical
비판적인
Wait.
기다리다.
What is this? What happened to you?
이게 뭔가요? 당신에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
I had a fight.
나는 싸웠다.
are you OK
괜찮으세요
I'm going to be in terrible pain tomorrow.
내일은 정말 고통스러울 것 같아요.
Why did you handcuff him in front? It will break it easily.
왜 그 사람 앞에서 수갑을 채웠나요? 쉽게 깨질 것입니다.
I do not think so
난 그렇게 생각하지 않아
Do they need to be tied up again?
다시 묶어야 하나요?
Tie him up quickly. Bring the cart, Gun-woo.
빨리 묶으세요. 수레를 가져와, 건우.
Good
좋은
Hold his feet.
그의 발을 잡아라.
Good. Let's go
좋은. 갑시다
- Our jackets. - Damn. quickly
- 우리 재킷 - 젠장. 빠르게
These are expensive.
이것들은 비싸다.
I handcuffed him here.
나는 그에게 수갑을 채웠습니다.
He escaped because you tied him to a pipe.
당신이 그를 파이프에 묶었기 때문에 그는 탈출했습니다.
You had to get good at restraining him.
그를 제지하는 데 능숙해야 했습니다.
Damn
젠장
"(Jang Do Im)"
"(장도임)"
What delayed you?
무엇이 당신을 지연시켰나요?
We hit a snag.
우리는 걸림돌에 부딪혔습니다.
And wealth?
그리고 부?
Don't worry. The money is still there.
괜찮아요. 돈은 아직 거기에 있습니다.
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
I can't reach InBome.
인보미에 연락이 안 돼요.
My face and mouth were badly cut,
얼굴과 입이 심하게 잘렸는데,
So I'll go through the emergency
그럼 긴급조치로 갈게요
Before I return to the site of the event.
행사장으로 돌아가기 전.
what do you mean
무슨 뜻이에요
Clean up your mess before you leave.
떠나기 전에 엉망진창을 정리하십시오.
Okay. You are right sir.
좋아요. 당신 말이 맞습니다.
But my face is bleeding badly.
그런데 얼굴에서 피가 심하게 나네요.
My teeth are loose, so I have to...
이빨이 약해서 그러려니 해야 하는데...
You damned bastard.
빌어먹을 놈.
Call Jung, gather his men and eliminate them immediately.
정을 불러 부하들을 모아 즉시 제거하라.
I want their heads, okay? I see you trying to hold back, you bastard.
난 그 놈들의 머리를 원해, 알았지, 네가 참으려고 애쓰는 게 보이네, 이 개자식아.
Screw you. Do you want to die?
엿먹어라. 죽고 싶나요?
Should I cut off your head before I cut off their heads, you idiot?
그 놈들의 머리를 자르기 전에 먼저 네 머리를 잘라버릴까, 이 바보야?
I will do what you ask.
나는 당신이 요청하는 것을 할 것입니다.
Sir
선생님
Move!
이동하다!
Get in the car quickly.
빨리 차에 타세요.
Arma!
아르마!
- Open the trunk. - Okay.
- 트렁크를 열어보세요 - 알았어
Push it!
밀어!
I notice
나는 눈치 채다
quickly
빠르게
Damn
젠장
Okay, we're done.
좋아요, 끝났습니다.
the curse. We have to get what's in the safe.
저주. 금고 안에 있는 것을 찾아야 해요.
Shouldn't we leave now?
이제 떠나야 하지 않겠습니까?
You are ahead of us.
당신은 우리보다 앞서 있습니다.
How many are there?
몇 개나 있나요?
Billions at least.
적어도 수십억.
I will help you.
내가 당신을 도울 것입니다.
- He preceded us. - Actually...
- 그 사람이 우리보다 먼저 왔어요 - 사실은...
We must come in billions.
우리는 수십억 달러를 벌어야 합니다.
Start the car and wait. We will be back quickly.
차에 시동을 걸고 기다리세요. 우리는 빨리 돌아올 것입니다.
You must hurry.
서둘러야 합니다.
- Woo Jin, there's a bag under the closet. - Okay.
- 우진아, 옷장 밑에 가방이 있어 - 알았어.
Wow! gold bar
우와! 골드 바
- Oh my God. Start packing it! - Okay.
- 맙소사. 짐 싸기 시작해 - 알았어.
Dollars?
불화?
Do not sit still. Pack it.
가만히 앉아 있지 마십시오. 포장하세요.
Good
좋은
the curse. Someone was severely beaten.
저주. 누군가 심하게 구타당했습니다.
Are you well
당신은 잘 있습니다
Follow me.
나를 따르라.
Slow down.
천천히 해.
Why is there so much money?
돈이 왜 이렇게 많아?
faster
더 빠르게
They are very heavy.
그것들은 매우 무겁습니다.
Good
좋은
Call Gun Woo.
건우에게 전화해.
Yes, Woo Jin.
응, 우진아.
Don't stop following me no matter what happens.
무슨 일이 있어도 나를 따르는 것을 멈추지 마세요.
Good
좋은
Damn
젠장
the curse
저주
Can you go faster, Gun-woo?
건우 씨, 더 빨리 갈 수 있나요?
I think the car is currently overloaded.
현재 차가 과적된 것 같아요.
When I give you my signal, you go ahead of me.
내가 신호를 보내면 당신은 나보다 먼저 가세요.
Good. I'll try
좋은. 나는 노력할 것이다
Get ahead of me now!
지금 나보다 앞서!
Damn
젠장
Screw it.
나사로 고정.
Ride fast.
빨리 타세요.
They are coming. Hurry more!
그들이 오고 있다. 더 서둘러요!
There's a disturbance in the car!
차에 소란이 생겼어요!
Damn
젠장
the curse
저주
Screw it. Hang on.
나사로 고정. 잠깐만요.
Damn
젠장
"Woo Jin!" Are you well
"우진!" 당신은 잘 있습니다
Let's go!
갑시다!
Push!
푸시!
more
더
"Woo Jin!"
"우진!"
Push it to the right!
오른쪽으로 밀어주세요!
Push! more
푸시! 더
Speed ​​up!
속도를 높여라!
- Shit. - She stopped.
- 젠장 - 그녀는 멈췄어요.
the curse
저주
The car broke down. Get down. We have to get the two bags.
차가 고장났습니다. 내려와, 가방 두 개를 가져와야 해.
Run!
달리다!
Run. quickly
달리다. 빠르게
Hey!
여기요!
Run faster!
더 빠르게 뛰어!
Translation of "Walid Muharram"
"왈리드 무하람"의 번역